Every time I get some money, I crash my car.
Every time I get some money, something in my house breaks.
Why?
Because our ancestors also carry some of these programs
that we inherit in our epigenetic field.
So back in the day, money is the root of all evil.
Anyone with money is bad.
Or if I have too much money, I'll grow apart from God.
And this person ends up carrying that belief,
no matter how hard they hustle,
no matter how much effort they put in,
no matter how much they know they want money,
that they want to be successful.
But it's like money just slips right through their fingers
because we're always validating our beliefs.
And our subconscious makes up 90% of who we are.